Lev Ki

Software Engineer, Game developer

Warsaw, Poland. Open to relocation lev.ki.contact@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/lev-ki/

I am a programmer with experience in both AAA and indie games. I've been creating games since 2015. I have experience supporting my team as a Scrum Master.

Making games is my passion, I love games as a creative medium. I am self-motivated and ambitious. I am a fast learner. I take ownership of my work and always advocate for maximum visibility in communication.

I love working with people and I always strive to improve the team environment as I believe that it is essential for long-term success.

Experience

CD Projekt Red, Poland - since February 2021

Next Installment in The Witcher Series - since January 2024

Gameplay Programmer (Unreal Engine 5, C++)

- Owning and developing new gameplay features on both technical and design sides
- Creating tools for designers with focus on good UX and smooth content creation

Cyberpunk 2077: Phantom Liberty And 2.0 Update - July 2022 - January 2024

Gameplay Programmer (REDengine 4, C++)

- Delivered gameplay features such as Perk Trees and Cyberware which were universally praised by both journalists and players
- Participated in game design discussions and owned parts of features mentioned above
- Supported the team as a Scrum Master

GWENT: The Witcher Card Game - February 2021 - July 2022 (1 year 6 months)

UI and Network Programmer (Unity, C#)

- Developed UI and Client-Side Network features of the game (C#)
- Owned technical design and development of one of the game modes
- Maintained and improved CI/CD, Automated processes that were previously causing issues, which led to smoother releases and reduced number of issues
- Handled update releases from the servers / network perspective

• Relocation to Poland

• Codee.Studio, Russia - February 2020 - November 2020 (10 months)

Multiple outsource projects

Game Developer (Unity, C#)

• As the only developer on the team, delivered an interactive product demonstration for a larger-scale third party

Independent Game Development - since 2015

Making all kinds of games. Alone and in different teams. On game jams and in my free time.

Skills

Programming: C++, C#, C, Python, Java, JS. Multiple other languages, and good at learning new ones **Game Engines:** Unreal Engine, Unity, REDengine 4, Godot

Other Skills: Game Design, Scrum, Leadership, Teamwork, Communication, Level Design, 3D modeling Languages: English, Russian

Education & Other Info

- Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science Bauman Moscow State Technical University, Russia Specialization: Robotics and Complex Automation, CAD (Computer-Aided Design)
 Bachelor's Thesis: Training Continuous Neural Networks Using Optimal Control Methods
- Professional Agile Leadership I (PAL I) certificate
- My hobbies and interests: running, journaling, photography, travel, self-improvement. And playing games, obviously

Up-to-date version: https://lev-ki.github.io/Resume/